《超女》前情提要
Previously on Supergirl...
现在是时候向那些
Now, it is time, you avenge yourself
辜负你的弟兄们报仇了
against the brother who wronged you.
-是你  -抱歉我毫无歉意
- You. - Sorry, not sorry.
你们敢信是新闻业拯救了世界吗
Can you believe the fourth estate saved the day?
卡拉·丹弗斯是超女
Kara Danvers is Supergirl.
你的朋友们从一开始就在骗你
Your friends have been lying to you.
-该死  -刹车失灵了
- Damn it. - The brakes.
救命  救命
Help! Help us!
谢谢你  超女
Thanks, Supergirl.
我长大后  想和你一样
When I grow up, I wanna be just like you.
那很简单  只要你为正义而战
Oh, that's easy, you just have to fight for what's right
并且永不说谎就行
and always tell the truth.
永不说谎  真有你的
Always tell the truth, that's rich.
卢瑟小姐
Ms. Luthor,
一切都好吗
is everything all right?
为何这么正式
Why so formal?
我还以为我们是好朋友
I thought we were best friends.
卡拉
Kara.
-你知道了  -知道什么
- You know? - Know what?
一个虚伪的家伙骗了我很多年吗
That you're a hypocrite who's been lying to me for years?
不是  莉娜  我没有...
No, Lena, I didn't-- -
结束
Terminate.
虚拟现实模拟结束
Virtual reality simulation terminated.
我能问您个问题吗  卢瑟小姐
May I ask you something, Ms. Luthor?
好的  霍普
Yes, Hope.
您在虚拟现实中运行的那些模拟
These simulations you've been running in virtual reality.
我的计算显示
My calculations show it's possible
它们都有可能在现实世界实现
they can be achieved in the real world.
凯特科的卡拉·丹佛斯
将被授予普利策奖
你是想帮我杀掉超女吗
Are you offering to help me kill Supergirl?
是的  您需要我帮忙吗
Yes. Would you like me to facilitate?
我感谢你的提议  霍普
I appreciate the offer, Hope.
你的智商和能力每天都在提升
You grow more intelligent and capable by the day.
你在协助我的同时  没有野心和自负  不会多事
And your assistance comes without ambition, drama, or ego.
-这正是您发明我的原因  -没错
- That's why you built me. - Precisely.
因为我相信科技  不相信人
Because I trust in technology, not people.
人会受情感支配
People are governed by feelings.
愤怒  伤痛  悲哀  我也有这个缺点
Anger, hurt, sadness, and I'm guilty of that too.
所以我才进行这些模拟
That's why I engage in these simulations,
来训练那些情感
to excise these emotions.
我不是坏人
I'm not a villain.
我不想杀死超女  我只想让她感受到
I don't want to kill Supergirl, I just want her to experience
她给我带来的那些伤痛
the same hurt she inflicted on me.
很快她就会体会到
And soon enough she will.
超 女
第五季 第一集
诺南咖啡
由黑曜石之北赞助
不好意思
Pardon me.
我还以为迟到了
Thought I was gonna be late,
但看起来我来的时间正好
but looks like I turned up just at the right time.
这些人是怎么了
What is going on with these people?
-他们完全不注意周边  -看他们银色的眼球
- They're completely oblivious. - By their silver eyes,
我想他们是斯拉托人
I would say that they were Slattorians.
我在调查时碰到过的外星人
A race of aliens I came across during an investigation.
你这次可推理错了  荣恩·荣兹
Oh, your PI powers of deduction are failing you, J'onn J'onzz.
银色眼球是黑曜石之北的产品
The silver eyes are courtesy of Obsidian North.
那不是你工作的公司吗  凯丽
Isn't that the company you're working for, Kelly?
今天是我第一天上班
Today is my official first day.
那些是增强现实隐形眼镜
Those are augmented reality contact lenses
正在测试阶段  那些有银色眼球
that we're beta testing. The people with the silver eyes
看着收银台上空的人
that are staring at the void above the cashier?
实际上他们在看虚拟菜单
They're actually looking at a virtual menu.
我演示给你看
I'll show you.
当你戴上隐形镜片后
So when you wear the contact lenses,
你与很多人在社交网络上建立了连接
you're linked to tons of people on a social media platform,
他们可以不说一句话就进行交流
and they can connect without saying a word.
有点像你和我
Kind of like you and me.
你们真恩爱
You guys are so cute.
但是那些隐形眼镜吓到我了
But those contact lenses creep me out.
等到你摆一下手就能投票时
Just call me when you can register to vote
再告诉我吧
with a gesture.
看  马上就要大选了
'Cause, look, there's about to be a special election,
但你们知道选民登记减少了吗
and did you know that voter registration is down?
人们不想关注
People don't wanna pay attention
现实世界发生的事了
to what's happening in the real world.
是  但是也有好事发生
Yeah, but, you know, some good things have happened
自从你的文章登出并扳倒贝克总统
since your article came out and took down President Baker,
揭露莱克斯·卢瑟
exposed Lex Luthor.
现在某人
And somebody...
明天要接受普利策奖了
is being presented with a Pulitzer tomorrow
因为是你帮助让这一切实现的
'cause you're the one that helped make it happen.
我的工作能被认同确实感觉很好
It does feel good to have my work recognized,
我只是以为在贝克下台后
but I just thought after Baker was ousted,
会有更多人迫切希望
more people would be hungry
并准备好进行社会变革
and ready to fight for social change.
现在却好像所有人都躲在科技产品后边
And now it just seems like everyone's hiding behind their gadgets.
科技也办成了很多好事  卡拉
Technology does a lot of good too, Kara.
我的新工作将会用到黑曜石的虚拟现实技术
In my new job, I am going to be using Obsidian's VR tech
来治疗老年痴呆与应激障碍病人的大脑
to heal the brains of dementia and  patients.
没错  我是个老顽固
Touche. I'm a curmudgeon.
你的新工作听起来很棒
Your new job sounds amazing,
我真高兴我们会在同一栋楼里工作
and I'm so glad we're working in the same building.
可以一起吃大肚腩汉堡午餐
Big Belly Burger lunches.
时间不早了  我该走了  各位
Ooh, look at the time. I gotta fly, guys.
我在教一班孩子太极
I'm teaching a Tai Chi class to a group of kids.
真棒  荣恩
Oh, that's wonderful, J'onn.
我现在活得通透  有目标
Yeah, I'm living with clarity and purpose.
-可棒了  -如果我第一天上班就迟到
- It's gonna be great. - You know what would not be great
那可就不棒了
is me being late for my first day.
-是啊  -好了  我该走了
- No. - Okay, I gotta run, bye.
-再见  -再见
- Bye. - Bye.
昨晚跟莉娜谈得顺利吗
Hey, how did it go with Lena last night?
我等不及想知道...
I mean, I'm dying to hear. -
不好  我知道这表情
Oh, no, I know that face.
你真的...  你什么都没说吗  你没告诉她吗
Are you ser-- You didn't say anything? You didn't tell her?
不是我的错  我得带狗去看医生
It's not my fault, I had to take the dog to the vet.
你根本没养狗  卡拉
You don't have a dog, Kara.
是我邻居斯坦因夫人的狗
My neighbor's dog. Mrs. Stein.
-得了吧  -她需要我的帮助
- Oh, come on. - She needed my help.
你得告诉莉娜你是超女
You have to tell Lena that you're Supergirl,
-但是  -我告诉你先别说的时候
- but-- - When I told you to hold off,
我只是指等一晚上
I just meant for one night.
但是有太多事发生了
But there's been so much going on.
我在报道大选
I'm covering the special election,
要送狗去看病  我还在帮你
and with the dog, and I'm helping you
抓回那些超查部沙漠分部里的犯人
recover all those prisoners from the DEO desert facility.
我和超查部非常感激你的付出
And the DEO and I very much appreciate that.
你给自己找了这么多事做
But you're doing all these other things
而你该做的事只有一件
when there's just one thing that you need to do.
我知道
I know.
只是我已经拖了这么久
I've just put it off for so long,
现在
and now...
因为我不懈追求真相
I'm being given an award
我即将获奖
for my tireless pursuit of the truth,
可我却是个骗子
and I'm a liar.
-我真可恶  -你不可恶
- I'm terrible. - You're not terrible.
你只是害怕
You're just scared.
我好怕
I am so scared.
我好怕她永远不会原谅我  艾丽克斯
I'm so scared that she's never gonna forgive me, Alex.
什么样的人
I mean what kind of person
会骗自己最好的朋友这么久
lies to their best friend for this long?
我告诉过你无数次了
Look, I...have told you a gazillion times,
你是我所认识的人中最勇敢的
you are the bravest person that I know.
知道吗  所以勇敢点告诉她
Okay? So, be brave and tell her.
你说得对
You're right.
我们今天约好吃午饭
Yeah, we're having lunch today,
-我今天就告诉她  -好
- I'll tell her today. - Good.
我信任你
I believe in you.
不  是汉尼拔
No, Hannibal Lecter,
出自《沉默的羔羊》和《穿普拉达的女王》
-他吃人  -米兰达·普雷斯丽
- he eats people. - Miranda Priestly.
米兰达·普雷斯丽  你是认真的吗
Miranda Priestly? Are you serious?
我像米兰达撅起的嘴唇一样认真
I'm as serious as the pursed lips of Miranda Priestly.
太好了  你们来帮我证明一下
Okay, good, you guys can help me prove a point.
谁是影史上最棒的反派
Who is is the greatest movie villain of all time?
出自《哈利波特》和《虎胆龙威》
-伏地魔  -汉斯·格鲁博
- Voldemort. - Hans Gruber.
居然毫无帮助
Impressively unhelpful.
看来你只能无条件接受我是正确的
Well, I guess you'll just have to accept that I'm right.
女友永远是对的这种地球习俗
This Earth custom that the girlfriend is always right
毫无逻辑又令人泄气
is illogical and frustrating,
但我可以入乡随俗
but I can assimilate.
准备好开始工作了吗  多克斯特工
Are you ready for work, Agent Dox?
-紧随你身后  丹弗斯局长  -很好
- Right beside you, Director Danvers. - Great.
-回见  布莱尼  -回见  尼娅
- Bye, Brainy. - Bye, Nia.
不好意思
Sorry.
-我们走吧  尼娅  -走吧
- Let's go, Nia. - Let's go.
大家听好  我不在乎篇幅长短
Now, listen, guys, I don't care if it's 500 or 5,000 words,
我们所能做的最重要的事
the most important thing that we can do
是对每个候选人的所有信息加以报道
is to report everything that we can find on each candidate.
这样我们的读者才能做出明智的决定
That way our readers can make an informed decision.
如果你们能深挖  或许你们
And if you dive deep, maybe you too
也能获得普利策奖
can win a Pulitzer.
你好  需要帮助吗
Hello, uh, can I help you?
除非你手里有测光表
Not unless you brought a light meter.
这间办公室急需太阳能窗大改造
This office is in dire need of solar window treatments.
不好意思  你是哪位
I'm sorry, who are you?
我的天  我真失礼
Oh, my God, I am so rude.
安德里亚·罗哈斯  你是
Andrea Rojas. And you?
卡拉·丹弗斯
Kara Danvers.
卡拉  幸会
Kara? Such a pleasure.
-我是你的粉丝  -你人真好
- I'm a big fan. - Oh, that's very kind of you.
你是黑曜石之北的罗哈斯吗
And did you say Rojas, as in Obsidian North?
独一无二
The one and only.
好的  不好意思  罗哈斯女士
Right, uh, well, I'm sorry, Ms. Rojas,
我想你乘电梯时下错楼层了
I think the elevator dropped you off on the wrong floor.
黑曜石公司在楼下
Obsidian's one down.
我的天
Oh, my goodness.
莉娜还没告诉你  对吗
Lena didn't tell you, did she?
-没告诉她什么  -詹姆斯·奥尔森
- Didn't tell her what? - James Olsen.
很高兴你来了  我很崇拜你
I am glad you're here. I'm a big admirer of yours.
千万不要以为
So don't think for one moment
我不会为你找到合适的位置
that I won't find a place for you here.
为我找到合适的位置
Find a place for me here?
我收购了凯特科
I bought CatCo.
其实我买下了整幢楼
Actually, I bought the whole building,
但凯特科是主要收购目标
but CatCo is the major acquisition.
我将接任总编一职
And I'm taking over as editor-in-chief.
欢迎来到"失落的氪星"展
Welcome to the Lost World of Krypton exhibit.
去吧  去看看
Go ahead, take a look.
大多数展品都是由超女和超人
Now, many of these items were generously donated
慷慨捐赠的
by Supergirl and Superman,
包括超人还是婴儿时来地球所乘的分离舱
including the pod that Superman flew to Earth in as a baby.
是不是很酷
Isn't that cool?
有谁想体验一下
Okay, now who wants to experience
幻影区
the Phantom Zone?
时间在那里不会流逝
Where time does not pass?
大伙快来  跟上我
Okay, come on, everybody, follow me.
孩子
Hey, kiddo.
快来跟上大家
Hey, come on and join us.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
什么
What?
卡拉
Kara.
总算见到你了  好久不见
Finally. It's been ages.
凯特科出什么事了吗
Hey, is everything okay at CatCo?
我有六通詹姆斯的未接来电
I have six missed calls from James.
事实上
Actually...
半小时前  安德里亚·罗哈斯
Andrea Rojas showed up in his office
到他办公室说她收购了凯特科
about a half an hour ago saying she bought CatCo?
-她为什么要那样做  -谢天谢地
- Why would she do that? - Oh, thank God.
我对詹姆斯和尼娅说肯定有大误会
I told James and Nia there must have been a huge mistake.
不是误会  卡拉  我
It's not a mistake, Kara, I...
把凯特科卖给安德里亚了
sold CatCo to Andrea.
但她答应过我  等我跟你吃过午餐
She wasn't supposed to show up till tomorrow
明天再过去
after you and I had had lunch.
你卖掉了凯特科  却没告诉我们任何人
You sold CatCo without telling any of us?
说实话  卡拉  我当初买下公司
To be honest, Kara, I only bought the company
是因为我知道它对你意义重大
because I knew how much it meant to you,
坦白地说  那造成了我资金短缺
and it's frankly left me strapped for capital,
而我正在进行的一项风险投资
which I desperately need for a new venture
迫切需要资金
that I'm working on.
安德里亚给我的条件让我无法拒绝
When Andrea called, it was just too good of an offer to pass up.
我不清楚这些情况
I... I had no idea...
-我完全理解  -安德里亚和我是故交
- I completely understand. - Andrea and I go way back.
我们在寄宿学校就认识了
I mean, since boarding school.
她是位非凡的商业女性
And she is a brilliant business woman.
假如我认为她不能胜任
I would not have sold her CatCo
绝不会把凯特科卖给她
if I didn't think she would do a great job.
当然
Oh, of course.
你为什么没提前告诉我
Why didn't you tell me beforehand?
我胆怯了
I was a coward.
我希望你不会觉得
And I hope that you don't feel like
我一直瞒着你
I made you out to be too much of a fool
是在愚弄你
by keeping you in the dark.
-不会  -你是我最好的朋友
- No. - You're my best friend,
而我再一次
and here I go, once again
证明你比我更善良
proving that you are more virtuous than I am.
但我从来没打算做圣人
But I never did purport to be a saint.
我叫了午餐外卖  应该很快就到
I've ordered some lunch in. It should be arriving soon.
不如你和我聊聊吧  你还好吗
Why don't you fill me in? I mean, how are you?
-最近怎么样  -我...
- How have you been? - Oh, I've, um...
其实我有一件事
You know what, actually there is something
想告诉你  我...
I wanna talk to you about, I...
卡拉  博物馆里有事发生
Kara, there's an incident at the museum,
-你能过去吗  -莉娜
- can you get there? - You know what, Lena?
很对不起
I'm-I'm so sorry,
我有一篇文章的重要线人想和我见面
a huge source for one of my articles is trying to meet,
要找到他难如登天  我得走了
he's impossible to pin down, I got... I have to run.
对不起
I'm sorry.
明天普利策奖典礼上见
I'll just see you tomorrow at the Pulitzer party.
好
Right, yeah.
这倒是头一回  真吓人
Well, this is new and terrible.
我们需要小行星的时候  它在哪呢
Where's an asteroid when you need one?
艾丽克斯说你可能需要我帮忙
Alex said you might need my help.
我们把恐龙降服吧
Let's get the dino.
荣恩  荣恩
J'onn, J'onn, hey, hey.
你能听到我说话吗
Can you hear me?
我从来没经历过这种事
I've never experienced anything like it.
霸王龙一定是让我精神瘫痪了
That T. Rex must've caused some kind of psychic paralysis.
有任何关于恐龙的情报吗
Any intel on the dinosaur?
是变形者
A shapeshifter.
-白火星人吗  -不是  否则我会知道的
- White Martian? - No, I would've known.
我觉得这个外星人不只是想乘分离舱跑路
I'm guessing this alien didn't want just another ride.
氪星分离舱利用反物质来推进它们穿越太空
Kryptonian pods use antimatter to propel them through space,
我知道这个猜测很大胆  但是...
and I know it's a long shot, but...
引擎能用来...
can the engine be used...
做炸弹吗
To make a bomb?
那要求高超的技巧以及庞大的资源
It would require great skill and enormous resources.
但这是有可能的
But it is possible.
破坏性如何
How destructive?
足以摧毁跨越三个太阳系的所有生命
Strong enough to destroy all life across three solar systems.
这下好了
Oh, well...
我们面临着一个更严重的问题
We face an even graver problem,
超女的披风毁了
Supergirl's cape has been destroyed.
是的
Oh, yes, uh...
我完全忘记了
I totally forgot about the risk to life
三个太阳系的生命岌岌可危
across three solar systems.
现在不是讽刺的时候
This is no time for sarcasm,
无论你的笑话多冷多幽默
however dry or well-crafted.
超女的披风专为高速的
Supergirl's cape is uniquely suited for the needs
超级英雄行动所设计
of high-speed superhero maneuvers.
相信我  当变形族从塔科隆盖托斯星球
And believe me, when a Farfarmniflatch is pursuing you
恶名昭著的监狱一路追击你的时候
across the poisonous prison pits of Takron-Galtos,
你会怀念以前那些
you will wish for those heady days of old
穿着披风可以急速右转弯的美好时光
when your cape allowed you for an easy sharp right turn.
没错
Oh, yes.
我
I...
我会修补你的披风
I shall repair your cape.
我们会忘记披风挂彩的灾难
And we will forget this sartorial disaster ever occurred.
我们会抓到幕后黑手
We'll get whoever's behind this.
阿根廷首都
我父亲负责布宜诺斯艾利斯的黑曜石总部
My father runs Obsidian headquarters in Buenos Aires.
他和伊隆叔叔的太空殖民竞争
He's consumed with the space colonization rivalry
弄得他身心疲惫
with Uncle Elon.
-马斯克  -这倒是对我有好处
- Musk? - Which works in my favor
因为我爸把整个虚拟
because Dad turned the entire virtual
和增强现实的业务都交给了我
and augmented reality business over to me.
这是我们的虚拟现实健身房
This is our VR gym,
我们的大客户可以在我们的办公室里
where our VIP customers can scale El Capitan
安全地攀登酋长岩
from the safety of our office.
如果他们和我一样
Or if they're like me,
也可以在圣保罗海滩上
they can do a couple of half-baked crunches
随便做几个卷腹
on the Sao Paulo beach...
同时浏览社交平台上的照片
...while scrolling through Instagram on their phones.
这里是我们新的医疗区
Here's our new medical wing.
我很高兴能拿到这个工作机会  罗哈斯小姐
I am so excited for this opportunity, Ms. Rojas.
是的
As you should be.
这是一个特殊的时刻
This is a special moment in time.
在今年之内  我下决心要让每家每户
I'm determined to have Obsidian tech in every household
都能拥有黑曜石科技
within the year.
这跟我的业务有冲突呢
Well, my worlds are colliding.
-莉娜  -看来你很有用人的眼光
- Lena. - I see you have a good eye for staffing.
你知道我只和最优秀的人做生意
Well, you know I only do business with the best.
你对我给你的合同满意吗
Are you enjoying the contacts I gave you?
我们能单独聊两句吗
Could we talk privately?
-我们说好的  -没错
- We had a deal. - That's right.
13亿美元买下凯特科全球媒体公司
CatCo Worldwide Media for $1.3 billion.
虽然我的董事会认为出价过高
A little more than my board thought it was worth,
但我心软  老朋友有需要  我就出手
but I'm a softie for an old friend in need.
我是在说我们谈好的条件
I'm talking about the deal
明天再公布我把凯特科卖掉的秘密
to keep the CatCo sale secret until tomorrow.
结果你已经走马上任了
Instead you're upstairs measuring the drapes.
抱歉我惹到你了
Well, I'm sorry I ruffled your feathers.
我以为早几个小时公布不会有什么区别
I didn't think a few hours would make a difference.
听着
Look...
我希望我们能有个良好的开端
I want us to start off on the right foot here.
凯特科并不是我们合作的终点
CatCo isn't the end all of what we can offer each other.
我同意
I agree.
如果我们要再次合作
If we are to have a relationship again,
而我要求你不要在24小时内透露某件事
and I ask you not to disclose something for 24 hours,
我希望你认真对待我的话
I expect you to take me at my word.
我做每件事都有我的目的
Everything I do has a purpose.
-明白了  -不要再制造惊喜了
- Understood. - Just no more surprises.
你答应给我的轰动新闻
And that big story you promised me,
能吸引全世界的眼球
the one that would draw every eyeball in the world
关注凯特科的网站
to CatCo's website?
然后你就不会再插手公司
So long your hands were kept clean of it.
我答应过你  明晚9点可以拿到
You'll get it tomorrow night at 9:00 p.m. as promised.
我说到做到
I keep my word.
看看这间办公室
This room, look at this room....
人才济济
It's practically overflowing with talent.
新闻业最优秀聪明的人物
Journalism's best and brightest.
明天  我们将迎来著名的威廉·戴
And tomorrow, we'll be joined by the renowned William Day.
-《泰晤士报》的那位吗  -是的
- From The Times of London? - Yes.
虽说我们已经羽翼丰满
Because as stacked as we are already,
但我们可以发展得更加壮大
we can always be bigger.
做到更强更好
We can always be stronger. We can always be better.
我们携手一起
And together,
将会创造一家世界级的新闻机构
we're gonna create a world-class news organization
推动消费者跨平台参与
that drives consumer cross-platform engagement.
对不起
I'm sorry, uh...
-消费者跨平台...  -参与
- consumer cross-platform... - Engagement.
瞩目度  营业额
Eyeballs, revenue,
各位目前的工作已然十分优秀
we're gonna take your already-brilliant work
我们会进一步精进你们的业务  做到极致
and we are gonna sharpen it until it's deadly,
然后我们再把它变现
and we're gonna monetize it.
我很尊敬您  罗哈斯女士
With all due respect, Ms. Rojas,
不过在这里
we don't allow revenue
我们不会让营业额来影响编辑决策
to drive editorial decisions here.
看得出来
And it shows.
一直以来都是你在掌控方向  詹姆斯
You've been running the ship, James.
订阅量发展如何
How's subscribership?
降低了
It's down.
谁希望这样呢
Who wants that?
丹弗斯女士获得普利策奖之后
When Ms. Danvers won the Pulitzer,
阅读量严重降低
readership tanked.
这让人们有种印象
It gives a certain kind of impression that
我们的报纸很迂腐
the paper is pedantic,
沉重  无聊  像作业一样
it's heavy, it's dull, like homework.
太夸张了吧
That's insane.
不  卡拉
No, Kara...
夸张的是你们通过品牌塑造
what's insane is branding a company
打造了一个让人们想点击关闭的网站
in a way that causes people to click away from the site.
新闻不在于点击量
The news is not about clicks.
一切都在于点击量
Everything is about clicks.
从《财富》五百强公司销售产品
From Fortune 500 companies selling their wares
到新妈妈发布宝宝生日的照片
to a new mom posting her child's birthday,
如今  价值的衡量标准就是点击量
today the measure of worth is on a click.
为了存活下去  凯特科需要转型
To survive, CatCo needs to pivot.
营业额直线下降的同时
Attention spans have plummeted
大家的注意力持续时间也大大缩短
along with revenues.
读者想要的是茶水间新闻
Readers want watercooler news
读来有趣  便于消化
that's just fun to read and just as easy to digest.
这...
That, um...
我认为我可以代表在座所有人说一句
I'm pretty sure I can speak for everybody in the room
如果你想做的就是这样的内容
when I say that if that is the kind of content that you wanna create here,
我们会走人
we will walk.
我们进公司不是为了做这个
This is not what we signed up for.
但本来就是
But it literally is.
你们都签订了全新的三年合约
You're all on a brand-new, three-year contract.
如果你们不打算
If you're not interested
帮助我让凯特科走向未来
in helping me drive CatCo into the future,
你们完全可以选择离职
you are more than welcome to side roll out of the car,
当然我也可以行使你们的竞业禁止条款
just as I am welcome to exercise your non-compete clauses.
我很不希望看到你们这样的人才
I'd hate to see such talent
永远离开新闻行业
be driven permanently from the business.
但如果这有违你们的心意
But if your heart isn't in it,
告诉我就行
let me know.
我讲完了
Well, that's it.
敬未来
Cheers to the future.
卡拉  我们找到了超人的分离舱
Kara, we found Superman's pod.
天哪
Jeez.
你说得对  布莱尼  披风损坏之后
You were right, Brainy, this cape damage
对空气动力来说很不利
is terrible for aerodynamics.
我一直往右边偏
I keep keeling over to the right,
差点摔进湖里
I almost landed in a lake.
别担心  我正在全力寻求解决办法
Well, fear not, I am deeply engaged in finding a solution.
不过  我们
And yet, that is the least of our problems.
超查部刚接收到了强烈的能量特征信号
The DEO just picked up a massive energy signature,
但是出乎我们意料  那并不是炸弹
and it's not a bomb like we thought.
而是自制的幻影地带投射器
It's a homemade Phantom Zone projector.
几周以来  幕后的人似乎一直在
Whoever built this seems to have been
从各类军械库  实验室和政府机构
stealing rare, high-security materials for weeks
偷盗戒备森严的罕见材料
from various armories, laboratories, and government agencies.
但没偷我们
But not from us.
分离舱的反物质引擎是最后一块拼图
The pod's antimatter engine was the final piece of the puzzle.
他们花了这么久时间建造幻影地带投射器
So they've spent weeks building a Phantom Zone projector,
将其打开
turned it on,
然后就放在那里吗
and just left it on the ground?
他们好像是故意让我们找到的
It's almost as if they wanted us to find it.
问题是  为什么呢
Only question is, why?
陷阱
Trap.
午夜面前  无所遁形
There is no hiding from Midnight...
我杀戮无数
...murderer of multitudes.
我是卡拉·佐·艾尔
I'm Kara Zor-El.
我母亲将许多人关进了幻影地带
My mother put many prisoners in the Phantom Zone,
我想你是来找我的
I assume you're here for me.
但是把你关起来的是她
But don't take your fury out on this planet
请不要因此迁怒于地球
just because she locked you up.
不是你母亲把她关起来的
Your mother didn't lock her up.
-是我  -荣恩·荣兹
- I did. - J'onn J'onzz.
那些是能量空洞
Those are energy voids.
会摧毁触碰到的一切
They destroy everything they touch.
你能穿过去吗
Can you phase through them?
我试试吧
I'll try.
超女  投射器
Supergirl, the projector.
她消失了
She's gone.
她会回来的
She'll be back.
没人知道午夜是谁
No one knows who Midnight is.
也不知道她来自哪个星球
What planet she's from.
有一天她突然出现在火星上
One day she just appeared on Mars
帮助白火星人战斗
to fight alongside the White Martians.
-为什么  -因为死亡是她的动力源泉
- But why? - Because she's fueled by death.
而白火星人也很愿意
And the White Martians were quite happy
让她自由处置我的同胞
to let her loose on my people.
你们怎么打败她的
How did you defeat her?
我记不清了
I can't remember.
你之前在博物馆里遭受了精神冲击
You're still recovering from the psychic trauma
还没有完全恢复
you experienced at the museum.
也许影响了你的记忆
It could affect your memory.
我认为这是私人恩怨  荣恩
This feels personal, J'onn.
曼彻斯特·布莱克花了一年时间
Manchester Black spent a year
对我发动无数私人攻击
launching personal attacks against me.
如果他都没能打败我  我什么都受得住
If I can survive him, I can survive anything.
我们还是得找到午夜
We still have to find Midnight.
我们不知道是谁把她带来这里  以及为什么
And we don't know who brought her here or why.
好消息是
The good news is,
这样一场激战绝对削弱了她的能力
a battle like that must have depleted her powers.
在她再次袭击之前  我们应该争取到了
I think we bought ourselves up to 24 hours
24小时的时间
before she's able to attack again.
好  我会全国巡视
Well, good, I'll circle the country
看看能不能趁她虚弱时找到她
and see if I can find her while she's still weak.
荣恩  你能不能变形去帮我领奖
J'onn, can you shapeshift and accept my award tonight?
请一定要答应
Oh, yes, please,
看你那么做超有意思
it's great fun to watch you do that.
卡拉  不行
Kara, no.
你一定要亲自去领奖
You are accepting that award.
而且我们都会看着你领奖
And we're all gonna be there to watch.
我们会找到午夜
We'll find Midnight,
用我们以前对付其他敌人的方式
and we're gonna face her the same exact way
对付她
that we face everything else.
齐心协力
Together.
你来我的办公室了  不错
This is nice, you in my office.
我都不知道自己以后还有没有办公室了
Well, I'm not so sure if I actually have an office anymore.
我在电梯里碰见卡拉了
Yeah, I ran into Kara in the elevator,
我跟她说我不能在上任第二天
and I had to tell her I couldn't join her crusade
就跟她一块
against my new boss
反对我的新上司
on my second day.
是
Yeah.
我会支持你们的决定
I'll support whatever you guys decide to do.
只是不能体现在行动上
Just mostly in the abstract.
我真的很骄傲
I'm just really proud of the company
我们在过去几年里打造出这样的公司
that we built over the last few years.
一家有力  严肃  一针见血的新闻机构
It's a strong, serious, hard-hitting news organization
真正地对人们的生活产生影响
that actually affects people's lives.
安德里亚对凯特科的设想
Whatever this vision Andrea has for CatCo,
不是我认识的凯特科
I don't recognize it.
我恐怕没法配合下去
And I don't think I can play that game.
那就不必
Then don't.
什么意思
What do you mean?
凯特科和新闻工作不是你的全部
CatCo and journalism isn't all that you are.
早在爸爸把相机交给你之前
You started helping people
你就已经开始帮助别人了
long before Dad put that camera in your hand.
我知道  你觉得不管什么问题
And look, I know that you think that you have to
你都该硬着头皮解决掉
muscle your way through everything.
但你也该给自己个机会  后退一步
But, for once, just take a step back
问问自己
and ask...
"詹姆斯·奥尔森想要什么"
"What does James Olsen want?"
-你想见我  -卡拉
- You wanted to see me? - Kara.
你应该很熟悉威廉·戴了
I believe you're familiar with William Day.
是  是
Yes. Yes.
久仰大名
Uh, by reputation.
我非常喜欢您的作品
I'm a big fan of your work.
您对哈特·艾尔·普尔土地征用权的报道
Your expose on eminent domain
相当出色
in Hart-el-pool, it was brilliant.
是哈特利普尔
It's Hartlepool.
我同意
I totally agree.
太阳能窗改造是个好主意
Solar window treatments are the way to go.
卡拉  我让威廉看了一下
Kara, I asked William to take a look at the few articles
詹姆斯说可以发表的几篇文章
James said we're ready to post.
你那篇关于州长提议的水税的文章
Your piece on the governor's proposed water tax
研究做得非常深入
is very thoroughly researched.
我让威廉重写了
I asked William to rewrite it.
你把引语放在第四段里
You buried the lede in the fourth paragraph,
讲没用的事实和背景  情感模糊
obscured emotion with unneeded facts and back story.
不必要的细节太多
Overloaded it with unnecessary detail.
那篇报道展现了这个问题的方方面面
That story laid out everything going on with the issue.
删减事实  不提供各方面信息
Cutting out facts, not disclosing every side,
文章就会自带偏见
that puts inherent bias in the piece.
每个故事或多或少都带有偏见
Every story has inherent bias, to some extent.
我以为起码你会同意这一点
I would think you of all people would agree with me.
你的报道很全面而且深入
Your reporting is comprehensive and in-depth.
我给《泰晤士报》写文章时
When I wrote for The Times,
就会按着《泰晤士报》的要求写
I wrote stories the way The Times wanted them.
用法语为《世界报》写文章也一样
Did the same for Le Monde, in French no less.
但给《每日邮报》
The Mail, however,
- 我写的就是通俗小报文章  -卡拉
- I wrote tabloid stock. - Kara,
如果你对我想要的风格有什么意见
if you're having trouble with the style I'm looking for,
威廉都可以替你重写
William can always rewrite you.
-没问题  加上我的署名就行  -当然
- I don't mind, as long as I get a shared byline. - Of course.
你接手的是一家著名的新闻社
You can't just take over a storied news outlet
不可以让它变成只为博人眼球的小报
and turn it into a pandering clickbait tabloid.
我可以啊
Actually, I can...
然后你会威胁我说  假如我辞职
And here's where you threaten me if I quit,
-你就在新闻业封杀我  -对
- you'll block me from the whole profession. - Correct.
我不会开除你
And I'm not gonna fire you.
我也不会离开新闻业
Well, I'm not leaving journalism,
如果我留下来  你就得习惯
so if I stay here, you should get used to the fact
我报道的新闻  我写文章的风格
that I will be reporting what I want
都会按照我的想法来
and writing it the way I want to.
我可以写得短一些  这方面我很灵活
I will try to be shorter, because I am flexible.
但我会跟你对着干
But I will fight you
每一次  每篇报道
every time on every story
我都要以正确的方式把它呈现出来
to make sure it is told the way it deserves to be told.
我绝不接受他重写我的文章
I will not tolerate being rewritten by him,
我也绝不允许别人遏制我发声
and I will not allow my voice to be silenced.
我没想过要遏制你发声  卡拉
I never had any intention of silencing you, Kara.
-问题解决  很好  -我省力了
- I'm glad we worked that out. - Good for me.
很好
Good.
我就跟安德里亚发了火
And then I just went off on Andrea.
我告诉她  我究竟怎么看待
I told her how I really feel
她对凯特科的预想
about her new vision for CatCo,
告诉她我什么能忍  什么不能
and I told her what I will and will not tolerate,
而且是当着新来那家伙的面
and I did it all in front of the new guy.
干得漂亮
Good for you.
你看  我能跟我新上司正面对抗
Yeah, I mean, I can stand up in front of my new boss,
但要我告诉莉娜事实
but with Lena, when it comes to telling her the truth,
我就语塞了
I'm just frozen.
我怎么就做不到呢
Why can't I do it?
我最近确实把你逼得太紧了
Look, I know I've been hard on you.
但是  你是今晚的主角
But you know what? Tonight, this is your night.
所以现在你也不要逼自己了
So I am giving you permission to stop beating yourself up
好好享受  行吗
and enjoy it, okay?
你可以迟点再考虑告诉她
You can worry about telling Lena another time.
你说得对
I guess you're right.
笑一个
Smile.
祝贺你  卡拉
Congratulations, Kara.
-谢谢  -我可以请你姐姐去跳支舞吗
- Thank you. - Do you mind if I steal your sister away for a dance?
当然  她很喜欢跳舞
No, of course. She loves dancing.
-我跳得不好  -失陪
- I am terrible. - Excuse me.
卡拉  我准备了礼物
Kara, I brought you a gift
庆祝你的光辉时刻
to celebrate this momentous occasion.
布莱尼  太谢谢你了
Oh, Brainy, that is so sweet of you.
其实不用的
You didn't have to do that.
我太兴奋了
I'm so excited.
瞧
Behold.
这是个微型运动激活器
It's a microscopic motion activator.
你忘带了吗
Oh, did you forget it?
它小到你看不见
It is simply too small to be perceived,
但你可别被它骗了
but don't be fooled,
这微型装置里藏着大家伙
for this miniscule device contains multitudes.
具体来说  就是你的新战服
More specifically, your new super suit.
布莱尼  我以为你只是修一下披风而已
Brainy, I thought you were just fixing my cape.
艺术家有自由发挥的空间
Well, give an artist a canvas,
我来帮你安装
if you'll allow me.
我能...  别弄坏了眼镜
Well, um, can I... Don't break them.
你在公共场合摘下眼镜时可要小心了
Now, please take care when removing your glasses in public,
因为下次你摘下眼镜时
for the next time you whip those off,
你的新战衣就会生成
your new suit will materialize.
或者根据需要而消失
Or dematerialize, as needed.
莉娜
Lena.
你怎么在这后面
What are you doing back here?
好吧  你逮到我了
Okay, you caught me.
这本该是一个惊喜
It was supposed to be a surprise,
我会介绍你出场
but I'm the one who's gonna introduce you.
我不能错过这个
I couldn't miss an opportunity
告诉世界你有多棒的机会
to tell the world how wonderful you are.
不  不  我
No, no, I...
莉娜  我不能让你这么做
Lena, I can't let you do this,
-我不值得  -你在开玩笑吗
- I don't deserve it. - Are you kidding me?
我比起其他人更知道这是你应得的
Me more than anyone knows how much you deserve it.
我看到你冒着生命危险揭露莱克斯的罪行
I saw how you risked your life to expose Lex's crimes.
我是超女
I'm Supergirl.
我一直都是超女
I've always been Supergirl.
我很早以前就应该告诉你  我知道
I should've told you so long ago, I know that.
但是我一直寻找借口
But I just kept making excuses
因为你被伤害了那么多次
because you've been hurt so many times
然后
and...
我说服自己这是在保护你
I convinced myself that I was protecting you.
但是有一天  你十分生我的气
And then one day, you were so angry with me,
生超女的气
with Supergirl.
但是你依旧爱着卡拉
But you still loved Kara.
我就一直在想
I just kept thinking...
如果我能只当卡拉
if I could be Kara, just Kara...
那我就能一直当你的朋友
that I could keep you as a friend.
我很自私  很害怕
I was selfish and scared,
我不想失去你
and I didn't wanna lose you,
所以我一直伪装自己
so I kept pretending,
从未停止
and I never stopped.
每次我对你保密  我不是
Every time I kept my secret from you, I wasn't...
在保护你  而是在伤害你
protecting you, I was hurting you,
就像其他人一样  对此我十分抱歉
just like everyone else, and I am so, so sorry.
对不起
I am so sorry.
拜托说句话吧
Please say something.
卢瑟女士  你两分钟后上台
Ms. Luthor, you're on in two minutes.
莉娜
Lena...
好的
Okay.
卢瑟女士  快到九点了
Ms. Luthor, it's almost 9:00 p.m.
要我将文件上传至凯特科服务器吗
Should I upload the file to CatCo's servers?
上传文件
卢瑟女士
Ms. Luthor?
世间充满了骗子
The world is full of liars.
充满了对我们隐瞒实情的人们
People who hide things from us.
充满了想操纵和控制我们的人们
People who manipulate and control us.
我当然知道
I should know.
毕竟全球顶尖的骗子中有一些是我的家人
Some of the best liars in the world are members of my own family.
但是在我的生命中
But in my life,
总有人一直在提醒着我
there was someone who always reminded me
真相是更好的途径
that truth was the better way.
她就是今晚我们在这里庆贺的人
And she is the person we are here tonight to celebrate.
卡拉·丹弗斯
Kara Danvers.
真相来之不易
The truth isn't easy.
胆小之人难寻真相
It's certainly not for the faint of heart.
但这是卡拉作为记者
But it is something that Kara, as a journalist,
每天都在不断坚持的事情
has pursued relentlessly every day.
因为她十分擅长此事
And because she's so good at it,
她让事情看起来很简单
she makes it look easy.
我们有时忘记了她也和我们一样
We sometimes forget that she's just like us.
但是锻造一条通往真相的道路
But forging a path to the truth
并不是件易事
isn't a piece of cake.
它犹如登山一般
It's more like climbing a mountain.
十分艰苦和困难
It's arduous and painful at times,
而就像我们一样
and, just like us,
卡拉有时会出纰漏
Kara can sometimes slip.
但是她总能重新振作
But she always gets back up
并坚持到最后
and pulls through in the end.
而我们总是会因为她的努力而变得更好
And we're always better for her efforts.
所以谢谢卡拉一直提醒我们
So, thank you, Kara, for reminding us
真相是如此重要
that the truth is important.
尽管真相有时并不容易接受
Even when it's not always easy to accept.
多克斯特工  我们有新进展
Agent Dox, we have an update.
卡拉
Kara.
你永远会是我最好的朋友
You will always be my best friend.
我刚收到了超查部的警报
I just received an alert from the DEO.
午夜充能完毕  正在行动
Midnight is fully charged and on the move.
-她在哪里  -在这里
- Where is she? - Here.
荣恩  带她远离平民
J'onn, lead her away from the civilians.
我们会跟上的
We'll follow.
看来该你上场了
I guess that's your cue.
超女
Supergirl.
裤子
Pants.
你们怎么换装这么快
How do you guys change so fast?
这可不妙
Well, that's not great.
她在干什么
What is she doing?
她在制造黑洞
She's creating a black hole.
布莱尼  如果我发射太阳耀斑
Brainy, if I solar flare,
能把那个摧毁吗
can I shut that down?
引力来自黑洞核心
Gravitational power comes from the core.
我们必须进入黑洞内部摧毁它
We'd have to go inside the void to do that.
但是为什么要那么费劲呢
But why do things the hard way?
荣恩
J'onn.
J'onn!
看来我们要用费劲的方式来解决了
Guess we're doing things the hard way.
不  你不可能既把荣恩解救出来
No, no, no, you cannot rescue J'onn from the event horizon
又摧毁黑洞
and destroy the void.
这件事的几率
The odds are--
我们不能让概率或是我们的恐惧
We can't let bad odds or whatever it is we're afraid of
阻止我们去做正确的事
stop us from doing what we know is right.
超女  不要
Supergirl, no.
我们不该都死在这里
We shouldn't both die in here.
我们不会的
We won't.
看
See?
小意思
Piece of cake.
凯特科全球媒体公司
你确定服务器没有出问题吗
And you're sure the server didn't go down?
因为我等的文件没有发过来
Because I was waiting on a file that didn't come in.
重新检查一遍
Well, check it again.
我以为你才是技术专家
Thought you were supposed to be the tech expert.
你来啦
There you are.
大怪洞开启时
You were at the party
你在派对上吧
when that big, weird hole opened, no?
照片呢
Where are the photos?
506分机的达定有你需要的东西
I believe Dardine at extension 506 has what you need.
我手上没有
I got nothing.
原因我可以说一大段
Now, I can go into a whole diatribe about why that is,
但我知道你喜欢精简
but I know you like to keep things short and sweet, so...
我不干了
I quit.
你确定吗
Are you sure about that?
你再也当不了记者了
You'll never work as a journalist again.
这是冒险的一部分
That's part of the adventure.
好吧  不  凯莉
Okay, no, Kelly,
你得帮我们做个最终评判
you need to settle something for us once and for all.
史上最强的电影反派是谁
Who is the greatest movie villain of all time?
很简单
That's easy.
汉斯·格鲁伯
Hans Gruber.
-我的宝贝  -怎么
- Oh, my heart. - What...
棒  早说了
Yes. Told you.
-拜  各位  -拜
- Bye, guys. - Bye.
明天见
See you tomorrow.
行
Okay.
我们得谈谈此事
We need to talk about this.
我们谈恋爱  或者说类似谈恋爱
We've been together or something like together
将近一个月了
for almost a month.
-将近  -可是
- Almost. - And...
我们的亲密接触还停留在握手
we still never get past a firm handshake.
我
I...
我只是得知道你的舒适区
I just need to know what you're comfortable with.
因为我感觉你可能还没
Because I get the feeling that maybe you haven't...
谈过恋爱
done this before.
你没谈过也没关系
Which is fine if you haven't,
-我完全理解  -你觉得
- I totally understand that... - You thought that...
-你谈过吗  -不是的
- Are you? - No.
我有过不少浪漫经历
I've had plenty of romantic experience.
-其实有很多  -好吧
- I mean, a lot, actually. - Oh, okay.
事实上
Truth is...
你是我第一个爱的人
you are the first person I have ever loved.
-布莱尼  -你想知道
- Brainy. - You want to know why
我为什么觉得米兰达·普雷斯丽很吓人
I find Miranda Priestly so terrifying?
因为她很冷淡
It's because she's cold,
很冷漠
she's uncaring,
她会背叛她最爱的人
she betrays the people she cares about the most.
上个月在莱克斯·卢瑟的营地
And last month at Lex Luthor's camp,
我就是那样对待你的
that is exactly how I behaved toward you.
-布莱尼  -虽然我爱你
- Brainy. - Even though I love you,
但我会伤害你
I hurt you.
我保持距离  是因为我发现自己
If I've kept my distance, it's because I find myself
想知道我怎样才会再次为你卸下心防
wondering how could I ever let my guard down with you again, I...
奎罗尔·多克斯
Querl Dox,
我了解你
I know you.
把我丢在营地的人不是你
That person who left me at the camp wasn't you.
你很体贴
You are caring,
无私
and selfless,
善良
and good.
我希望成为让你卸下心防的人
I want to be the person you let your guard down with.
我希望你能够
I want you to be able to...
在我面前完全做自己
fully be yourself with me.
你也希望那样吗
Do you want that too?
非常希望
More than anything.
那吻我吧
Then kiss me?
你迷路了吗
Are you lost?
没有  荣恩·荣兹
No, J'onn J'onzz.
我就在我应该在的地方
I'm exactly where I should be.
你是释放午夜的那个变形者
You're the shapeshifter that released Midnight.
你想怎样
What do you want from me?
让你罪有应得
To be punished for your crimes.
你也许打败了午夜
You may have defeated Midnight,
但我会确保你将罪有应得
but I'll make sure you get what you deserve.
为什么  你是谁
Why? Who are you?
别装作不认识我
Don't pretend you don't recognize me.
兄弟
Brother.
我没有兄弟
I have no brother.
错
Lies.
你和父亲比我认为的更邪恶
You and Father are more evil than even I knew,
但邪不压正
but justice will prevail.
我会以牙还牙
I will do to you as you did to me.
你说你是我的兄弟
You say you're my brother...
证明给我看
Prove it!
莉娜  我无法表达你今晚来这
Lena, I can't tell you how much it means to me
甚至还愿意跟我说话
that you were there tonight,
这对我有多重要
that you're even willing to talk to me at all.
谢谢你告诉我真相
Thank you for telling me the truth,
但是  卡拉
but, Kara,
事情回不到以前了
things can't be like they were before.
你懂吗  我们之间不能有秘密
Do you understand? There can be no more secrets between us,
-我得完全了解情况  -会的
- I have to be in on everything. - You will be.
所以我来了
That's actually why I'm here.
你现在知道了一切
You know everything now.
如果你需要我
And if you ever need me,
只需要打个电话
all you have to do is call.
文件准备好上传了
The file was ready to upload.
你为什么不发送
Why didn't you send it,
向全世界揭露超女的身份
exposing Supergirl's identity to the world?
你原谅卡拉·丹弗斯了吗
Did you forgive Kara Danvers?
她背叛了我
She betrayed me.
我心碎了
It broke my heart.
我绝不会原谅她
I could never forgive her.
-那我就不懂了  -你怎么会懂
- Then I don't understand. - How could you?
你又不是卢瑟家的人
You're not a Luthor.
我们是记仇的天蝎
We're scorpions.
有人背叛我们  我们就蛰人
When someone betrays us, we sting.
但我有个使命  霍普
But I have a calling, Hope,
那就是拯救人类
and it's to fix mankind.
我从没想到超女会告诉我她的身份
I never thought Supergirl would tell me who she was,
但既然她说了  我就有了机会
but now that she has, I have an opportunity,
我可以利用超女达成我的目的
and I can use Supergirl to achieve my ends.
她相信我们彼此信任  这么做就更简单了
That is easier to do if she believes there is trust.
准备模拟
Load the simulation.
是  卢瑟女士
Yes, Ms. Luthor.